Hello and welcome to programming fundamentals,
你好，欢迎学习编程基础知识，
the first course in an introduction to programming in C.
这是 C 语言编程入门的第一门课程。
I'm Drew Hilton and I hope you're ready to learn a lot about programming.
我是 Drew Hilton，我希望你已经准备好学习很多关于编程的知识。
>> And I'm Anne Bracy and I would like also to welcome you to this course and
>> 我是 Anne Bracy，我也想欢迎你参加这门课程和
specialization.
专业化课程。
I'm excited that you have the chance to come learn to program with us.
我很高兴你有机会来和我们一起学习编程。
>> And I'm Genevieve Lipp.
>> 而且我是 Genevieve Lipp。
I learned to program in C from Drew and Ann's book that this specialization is
我从 Drew an
based on, and can tell you first hand that it is a great way to learn.
d Ann 的书中学会了 C 编程，这个专业就是以此为基础的，可以直接告诉你这是一种很好的学习方式。
You don't need any prior background in programming,
你不需要任何预先的编程背景，
just an eagerness to learn and excitement about thinking through problems.
只需要渴望学习和对思考问题的兴奋。
>> As Genevieve just mentioned,
>> 正如 Genevieve 刚才提到的那样，
this specialization is great if you're new to programming.
如果你不熟悉编程，那么这个专业非常棒。
You might be thinking bout learning for wide a variety of reasons.
你可能出于各种各样的原因考虑学习。
Maybe you want to become a professional software developer, if so
也许你想成为一名专业的软件开发人员，如果是的话，
this is a great starting point.
这是一个很好的起点。
We're going to build solid fundamentals that will server you well in both C and
我们将建立扎实的基础知识，以便在 C 语言和
any other language.
任何其他语言中都能很好地为你服务。
>> Or maybe you want programming skills to use in some other discipline.
>> 或者，也许你想在其他学科中使用编程技能。
I know a lot of social scientists and
我认识很多社会科学家和
natural scientists who have found programming necessary,
自然科学家，他们发现编程是必要的，
to analyze the data that they have to explore the problems in their field.
以分析他们所拥有的数据来探索各自领域的问题。
>> Some of you may have already taken an intro course and
>> 你们当中有些人可能已经上了入门课程，并
be looking to expand your skills.
希望扩展自己的技能。
This can be a great chance to both build your programming skills from solid
这可能是一个很好的机会，既可以从扎实
fundamentals And to learn a new language.
的基础知识中培养编程技能，又可以学习一门新语言。
>> Another great reason to take this specialization is if you were taking
>> 选择这个专业的另一个重要原因是，如果你正在上
a computer organization class, either on Coursera, or
计算机组织课，无论是在Coursera上还
in school, and don't have the C programming background to excel.
是在学校里，并且没有C编程背景可以脱颖而出。
This specialization is a great way to come up to speed on those topics.
这个专业化是快速了解这些话题的好方法。
>> So what's special about the way that we're going to teach you?
>> 那么我们要教你的方式有什么特别之处呢？
We're going to start from the very beginning.
我们将从头开始。
A lot of programming courses assume you can just figure out how to write code from
许多编程课程都假设你可以通过
seeing a few examples.
看几个例子来弄清楚如何编写代码。
We aren't going to do that.
我们不会那样做。
>> Instead,
>> 取而代之的是，
we're going to teach you a step-by-step approach to solve programming problems.
我们将教你一种解决编程问题的分步方法。
This seven step approach is a great way to tackle any programming problem.
这种七步方法是解决任何编程问题的好方法。
From smaller ones that you'll use as practice in this course,
从你将在本课程中用作练习的小型，
to large complicated ones that you will use in real life situations.
到你将在现实生活中使用的复杂的大型。
>> We're also going to teach you how to read code as well as how to write it.
>> 我们还将教你如何阅读代码以及如何编写代码。
After all, how can you write if you can't read?
毕竟，如果你不会读书，你怎么能写呢？
For every piece of syntax that we teach you,
对于我们教给你的每段语法，
we are also going to teach you the semantics, what exactly the code does.
我们还将教你语义，代码到底是做什么的。
For any code you write,
对于你编写的任何代码，
you will be able to execute it by hand, saying exactly what every line does.
你都可以手动执行它，准确地说出每行的作用。
>> Which goes hand in hand with the principle of no magic.
>> 这与没有魔法的原则并驾齐驱。
We're never going to tell you to write or do a thing just because.
我们绝不会仅仅因为而叫你写作或做某件事。
Instead, we want you to learn that everything in programming is about well
相反，我们希望您了解编程中的所有内容都与明
defined rules, which you can understand and follow, or even execute yourself.
确定义的规则有关，您可以理解和遵循这些规则，甚至可以自己执行这些规则。
>> So, where do we go from here?
>> 那么，我们要从这里走向何方？
The rest of this course is all about computational thinking.
本课程的其余部分全部是关于计算思维的。
You'll learn a lot of important concepts,
你将学习很多重要的概念，
how to design an algorithm to solve a problem,
如何设计算法来解决问题，
how to execute a piece of code by hand, and the, Everything is a Number Principle.
如何手动执行一段代码，以及 “一切都是数字原理”。
These will lay the foundation for you to start writing programs in C in Course 2.
这将为你在课程 2 中开始用 C 编写程序奠定基础。
>> Speaking of Course 2, that is where you will learn to use
>> 说到课程 2，你将在那里学习使用
a variety of tools that are important to develop your code.
对开发代码很重要的各种工具。
You'll learn things like how to turn your code into an actual program that
你将学习一些东西，比如如何将你的代码变成
the computer can run, which is called compiling.
计算机可以运行的实际程序，这称为编译。
You'll also learn about testing and debugging, finding and
您还将学习如何测试和调试、发现和
fixing mistakes in your program.
修复程序中的错误。
>> In Course 3, you will learn about ways to store more complex data using pointers,
>> 在课程 3 中，您将学习如何使用指针、
arrays and strings.
数组和字符串存储更复杂的数据。
If you don't know what these are now no problem we'll explain them
如果你现在不知道这些是什么没问题，我们会在
when we get there.
到达那里时解释一下。
>> And in Course 4 we'll learn how to interact with the user and
>> 在课程 4 中，我们将学习如何与用户和
the system, as well as how to dynamically allocate memory
系统交互，以及在
when you don't know in advance how much data you have to work with.
您事先不知道需要处理多少数据时如何动态分配内存。
So, let's get started.
所以，让我们开始吧。